Phillia Mukengeshayi

Cape Town, South Africa | Phone: 081 323 5149 Portfolio website: www.phillia.co.za

Email: philliamuke@gmail.com
LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/philliamukengeshayi

SUMMARY

An organised and hardworking professional with over 3 years of experience in B2B account management and business development. Fascinated by all things technology (software development, cloud, security) and overseeing a portfolio of five key enterprise accounts worth annual revenue of +£200,000. Looking to leverage my business acumen and web freelancing experience with front-end technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript) to help with software development efforts. Obtained Bachelor's Degree in Information Science.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Account Manager - Network Sunday

Brighton, United Kingdom (Remote), AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

- Oversee a portfolio of 5 key enterprise accounts worth annual revenue of +£200,000.
- Manage ABM strategy of content programmes themed around cloud, cybersecurity, payments API, digital transformation, network infrastructure, supply chain 4.0 and geospatial software
- Crafted innovative ideas for business process improvement and internal training programs.
- Grew to help with the onboarding of 2 new account managers and 1 lead development rep.
- Initiated upselling opportunities, revenue retention & account growth. Clients include: Modulr Finance, BT Ireland, Mindtree, HCL Technologies, Tata Communications, IQGeo, Exceedra, Akamai

Web Developer - Freelancer

(Remote), OCT 2020 - PRESENT

- Built an online personal portfolio, Firefox and Netflix clone lwebsite using HTML, CSS, JS (NodeJS, React.is). www.phillia.co.za
- Help create new UX-friendly, responsive websites or update, fix or improve existing sites. I've worked
 on projects for entrepreneurs and their small companies. I've also worked on websites based in Wix as
 well as WordPress.

Service Delivery Manager - Network Sunday

Brighton, United Kingdom (Remote), DECEMBER 2019 - JULY 2021

- Exceeded KPIs by coordinating +100 interviews with C-level and executive leaders
- Delivered value to clients by setting up exploratory sales meetings and leads
- Collaborate with Account Managers and Directors on how to wrap up pilot campaigns in 3-6 months.
- Mentored offshore Research Associates through company content brand, TechPros.io.
- Liaised with management to prioritise client renewals and was promoted to Account Manager.

Client Acquisition Consultant - Meltwater

Cape Town, South Africa, NOVEMBER 2018 - NOVEMBER 2019

- Manage a database of self-sourced leads to develop relationships with potential prospects
- Conduct daily product demos demonstrating the value of media intelligence software
- Executed the entire sales process and liaised with C-Level Executives
- Consulted prospective customers to understand problems and used product knowledge to tailor SaaS media intelligence solutions resulting in revenue of R500,000 in 6 months.
- Recognised as the first consultant to successfully sell to Egypt from the South African office.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS (Bootstrap and SASS), JS (React.js): Built portfolio, paid-for projects & clone websites.
- Visual design: Worked off mock-ups in Figma and delivered responsive web designs.
- Content Management Systems: WordPress and Wix.
- Testing/Debugging: Git, Command-Line and Chrome Developer Tools, Postman.
- Project Management: Discord, Asana, Trello.
- Working knowledge of SDLC, CI/CD, Test-Driven Development and scrum/agile methodologies.
- Well-organised team player that enjoys collaboration
- Great communicator with public speaking skills fluent in French and English.
- Demonstrated leadership skills with the ability to work in an innovative environment.

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATES

Bachelor of Information Science - University of Pretoria (NOVEMBER 2017) *x2 Recognised as Top 15% of Golden Key International Honour Society*

Courses included:

- Digital repositories, user studies and dissemination
- Competitive intelligence and business management
- Information and knowledge management
- Experiential learning project (internship for information auditing)

Certificates

- Responsive Web Design FreeCodeCamp (AUGUST 2021)
- The Web Developer Bootcamp Udemy (JULY 2021)
- HTML Essential Training LinkedIn Learning (NOVEMBER 2020)
- Learning ECMAScript 6+ LinkedIn Learning (NOVEMBER 2020)

PERSONAL

- Location: Cape Town, South Africa
- ID Status: RSA ID
- Interests: Reading, Crypto, Football, Formula1, Running

REFERENCES

Available upon request